purpletrail.com 2008-12-18

# PurpleTrail Free Online Invitations Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy as of October 1st, 2007.

At PurpleTrail we recognize that privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use PurpleTrail's services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. To adhere to the highest standard of privacy, we have based our policy on that of [Google's](http://www.google.com/privacy.html)

PurpleTrail adheres to the US safe harbor privacy principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access and Enforcement, and is registered with the [U.S. Department of Commerce's safe harbor program](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/). 

## Personal information and other data we collect

"Personal information" is information that you provide to us which personally identifies you, such as your name, email address or billing information, or other data which can be reasonably linked to such information by PurpleTrail. 

  * PurpleTrail collects personal information when you register for a PurpleTrail service or otherwise voluntarily provide such information. We may combine personal information collected from you with information from other PurpleTrail services or third parties to provide a better user experience, including customizing content for you.
  * PurpleTrail uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use PurpleTrail services in order to improve the quality of our services.
  * PurpleTrail's servers automatically record information when you visit our website or use some of our products, including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request.

## Uses

  * We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising.
  * We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve PurpleTrail technologies and services.
  * We may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties outside of PurpleTrail.
  * Except in limited circumstances, we do not share personal information with third parties. In rare circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * PurpleTrail processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country.

If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us.
